2star.tv 2016-10-14

# Privacy Policy - 2Star

Please read this Privacy Policy (last revised as of November 1, 2015) before using this service. By continuing to use 2Star.tv, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to the terms of this policy.2Star, LLC., the operator of www.2Star.tv (the “2Star Website,” referred to as “2Star,” “us,” “we” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users, and we want you to be aware of how we use information that we have collected from and about you. By coming to the 2Star Website, you are agreeing to and accepting this Privacy Policy as well as the [User Agreement](http://2star.tv/terms) governing our services. Because the Internet is a rapidly evolving medium, and enhancements to the services we provide may affect the information that we collect and the manner that we use it, the Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If it does, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the 2Star Website, with an indication of the date of the most recent revisions.

You should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to the 2Star Website. Any websites linked to from the 2Star Website, an advertisement or an article displayed on the site are governed by their own privacy policies.

### What personally identifiable information do I provide to 2Star, and how does 2Star use it?

  * Personally identifiable information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate you. 2Star collects only the personally identifiable information that you provide to us if you register as a registered user on the 2Star Website, such as your name and e-mail address.
  * 2Star uses your personally identifiable information to communicate with you regarding your account or the 2Star Website. These communications may include, without limitation, notices regarding material changes to the 2Star Website’s policies, service updates, and service enhancements. Since these account-related communications are necessary to ensure we provide our users with the highest quality of services, our users are not permitted to opt out from receipt of these communications.
  * 2Star may also use personally identifiable information to e-mail you newsletters or tips about how to use the service, inform you of product updates, or notify you about our own special offers or those of our third-party partners. You may choose at any time to opt out of receiving some or all of these communications by emailing us [here](http://2star.tv/contact) or by using the unsubscribe link on any e-mail message you receive.
  * In order to improve and create a more customized experience, 2Star associates your personally identifiable information with information about your use of the website.

### What other information is collected about me on the 2Star Website and by whom?

  * Like most websites, 2Star employs cookies to recognize you and your access privileges on the 2Star Website. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store in a designated file on your computer. When you visit a site, that site can access only the information which it stored in your cookie – not information put on your computer by other web-based services.
  * 2Star maintains internal logs of users’ use of the 2Star Website. Logs include information such as IP address, browser type and version, and computer operating system. 2Star uses logs mainly for systems administration and diagnostic purposes, and to detect improper use of the site. Logs may also be used to generate aggregate, non-personally identifiable information for advertisers or other third parties.
  * 2Star may also contract, from time to time, with third parties to help us understand how people use our website and to provide functionalities such as email distribution, ad serving, customer surveys, comments, and content sharing. These companies also use cookies. They may also use other tracking technologies, such as web beacons (also known as clear GIFs, web bugs, tracking pixels or action tags), which are similar in function to cookies, allowing them to determine when users have reached particular web pages on the 2Star Website.
  * Cookies and web beacons allow 2Star and its third-party service providers to collect and analyze aggregate information about how its website is used.
  * We sell advertising on our site so that we can provide our service for free. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Information about your visit, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. Please be aware that if you opt out of allowing our web advertising partner to collect this information, you may not be able to use certain parts of the site nor have access to certain functions.

### How is my personally identifiable information or site usage data used?

  * 2Star may share your personally identifiable information with others under the types of circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to assign, sell, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party your personally identifiable information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer of all or substantially all of our assets.
  * We may make personally identifiable information available without your prior written or electronic consent, as required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority.
  * Advertisements, promotional offers, promotional e-mails, newsletters, “free gifts,” and links, for example, on the 2Star Website or sent via e-mail or other means from 2Star may ask for personally identifiable information from you. If you choose to provide this information, your personally identifiable information may be provided (either directly from you or by 2Star) to the advertiser or website or company making the offer or providing the gift. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy and information practices of those advertisers or websites linked to the 2Star Website.
  * 2Star may use other companies and persons to perform certain functions for us. These functions might include, for example, providing customer service and sending e-mail. These other companies and persons may have access to customer information (such as personally identifiable information) that is needed to perform their functions, but they are not authorized to use it for any other purposes. In addition, we may share information with other affiliated companies and joint ventures.
  * We may use and/or distribute information about you and your use of the 2Star Website in ways that do not identify you individually or reveal your identity.
  * Demographic information provided by you may be used, among other things, to tailor your user experience at the 2Star Website, distribute and show you content that we think you might be interested in, and display site content according to your preferences.

### How secure is my personal information?

  * We are very concerned about the security of customer data. All personal information is password protected and all passwords are encrypted.

### How will I know when there are changes to this Privacy Policy?

  * This Privacy Policy is subject to modification from time to time at 2Star’s discretion. All changes will be incorporated into the written policy and posted on the privacy policy pages of the 2Star Website. The date of last revision to the policy is indicated at the top of the document.

### What if I have questions that are not answered here?

If you have questions, you may contact:

2Star, LLC.  
123 Tran Duy Hung, Ha Noi

Attention: General Counsel[Or, use this form.](http://www.2star.tv/contact)
